http://www.xensor.nl/privacy-policy

Cookie and privacy policy
Xensor Integration is subjected to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Xensor is committed to protecting your rights to privacy. We have adopted and implemented this privacy statement as part of our ongoing commitment to protecting your personal information and as outlined in the GDPR.
Use of cookies on this website
We use the standard "cookie" feature of major browser applications that allows us to collect data about your visit to our website. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard-drive when you visit certain websites, thereby “tracking” your use of the site. Some browsers can be set to reject all cookies; if you choose to set your browser to reject cookies, some pages of the website may not function properly. At present we do not use cookies to collect Personal Information and we do not link the information that we collect using cookies to any personal information and we do not link the information that we collect using cookies to any personal information. We use the information gathered through the use of cookies to help us identify the areas of our website that are useful and which areas need improvement.  We may use your Internet Protocol Number (the number assigned to your computer while it is on the Internet) (“IP number”) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP number is used to gather broad, aggregate demographic information; however we do not link this information to personal information. In other words, even though your session may be tracked your identity will remain anonymous.
Contact Us
If you have any concerns or questions about this Privacy Statement, our privacy practices or if you would like to access, update or amend the personal information that we have on file about you, please feel free to contact our Privacy Officer.
© 2019 Xensor Integration
Distributieweg 282645 EJ DelfgauwThe Netherlands
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. + 31 (0)15 257 80 40
Cookie and privacy policy
Terms and conditions of delivery
Webdesign
